toolkit.com 2011-05-25

# Privacy Policy: Business Owner's Toolkit

### **Vendor Price Quotes**

Get Free quotes from leading vendors. No obligations.  [Learn more]

| Categories:  
---|---  

This Website is owned and operated by Toolkit Media Group, a Wolters Kluwer business. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. Toolkit.com respects the privacy of the users of our products, services, and Website, and we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. **To that effect, we have instituted the following Privacy Policy, which discloses what information we gather and how we use it:**

By using this Website, you agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via this Website, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect how we gather and manage your information. All changes to this Privacy Policy are effective upon posting to this Website without notice to you. You are responsible for regularly reviewing this Privacy Policy.

### Gathered and Tracked Information 

We gather the following types of information about users:  

  * Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions or via purchases made in the Toolkit Store. We collect information when users voluntarily register to become Toolkit.com Members, opt to receive our electronic newsletters, choose to e-mail content to a friend, participate in polls and surveys, or make purchases in the Toolkit Store.
  * Information gathered through aggregated tracking is derived mainly by tallying page views throughout this Website. This information allows us to better tailor our content to users' needs and to help us and our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience. As discussed below, we share certain aggregated data with our advertisers, sponsors, and partners.
  * Anonymous and non-personal information collected via "cookies" and other devices (as described below).

### Membership and Subscription Policy

We offer users the ability to register to become Toolkit.com members. Toolkit.com offers two types of membership, Free Membership and Premium Membership. Toolkit.com Terms and Conditions and other aspects of Membership are outlined in the [Toolkit.com Website Terms of Use](http://www.toolkit.com/terms.aspx). In order to register for Free Membership, you are required to provide your e-mail address, a username, a password, and the state where you are located. We ask for additional optional information on you and your business, such as your name, contact information, and certain characteristics of your business. You can also choose to subscribe to our free electronic newsletter.

In order to register as a Premium Member, you are required to provide the registration information outlined above and purchase the Premium Membership via the Toolkit Store. When you become a Premium Member of Business Owner's Toolkit, you will be asked to provide personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, phone, e-mail address, and credit card number as well as to select a password for accessing the Premium Membership items you select.

### Toolkit Store Policy

The Toolkit Store is an e-commerce platform allowing users to purchase products and services directly via the Toolkit Store or by clicking through to a participating third party vendor's Website. In order to purchase products or services from the Toolkit Store, users will be required to provide personally identifiable information in order to complete the transaction and for us to fulfill the order. While the terms and conditions of different products and services may require users to provide different information, the Toolkit Store typically collects the user's name, address, phone number, e-mail address, and credit card information.

In cases where users purchase products or services in the Toolkit Store that are fulfilled by third parties, the user's personally identifiable information that is necessary for order fulfillment will be shared with that third party in order to fill the order. The Toolkit Store will state when products or services are purchased directly via the Toolkit Store but are fulfilled by a third party. In cases where users leave the Toolkit Store and connect to a third party's Website in order to complete the purchase of products or services featured in the Toolkit Store, please be aware that we do not control the third party Websites and that this Privacy Policy does not apply to such third party sites. Users are advised to read the privacy policies and terms of use for such third party Websites prior to completing their order. These third party sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personally identifiable information. You should contact these third parties directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect. We make no promises or guarantees regarding, and we are not responsible for liable for, the data collection or privacy practices of the Websites that are not owned or operated by us. Toolkit Store policies are outlined in the [Toolkit.com Website Terms of Use](http://www.toolkit.com/terms.aspx).

### Electronic Newsletters Policy

Toolkit.com offers a free electronic newsletter to users who choose to subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter, which directs users to the subscription management page.

### "E-mail This to a Friend" Policy

Toolkit.com users can choose to electronically forward a link, page, or document to another party by clicking " **e-mail this to a friend** ". In order to electronically forward the content, the user must provide his/her e-mail address and the email address of the recipient. This information is only used for transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the e-mail. The information is not used for any other purpose.

### Polling

Toolkit.com may offer interactive polls to users so they can easily share their opinions with other users and see what our audience thinks about important issues. Opinions or other responses to polls are aggregated and are not identifiable to any particular user. Toolkit.com may use a system to "tag" users after they have voted, so they can vote only once on a particular question. Voting information is not used for any other purpose and is not correlated with information about individual users.

### Surveys

This Website may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We may share the aggregated demographic information collected in these surveys with our sponsors and advertisers. We never share any individual user survey information with third parties.

### Protection of Personally Identifiable Information

Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, all personally identifiable information provided when users register for membership or purchase products or services in the Toolkit Store is encrypted with secure server software to protect such information from unauthorized access. Your personally identifiable information, including your credit card information, username and password, will remain encrypted within our database. We continually work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. For orders placed directly with Toolkit Media Group in the Toolkit Store, we reveal only the last four digits of your credit card number when confirming an order, although we transmit the entire credit card number to our credit card processor in order to process the order.

We take reasonable steps to protect your personally identifiable information as you transmit your information from your computer to our Website and to protect such information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error-free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this site may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail. Moreover, it is your responsibility to safeguard your passwords, ID numbers, or other special features used to access this Website.

### User Tracking

Toolkit.com automatically tracks user traffic patterns throughout the entire site; however, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. We break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser).

Toolkit.com occasionally tracks and catalogs the search terms that users enter in our Search function to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We never track searches of individual users or what individual users read. Instead, we track how well each page performs overall, which helps us continue to improve services for you.

We also compile statistics that show the daily number of visitors to our site, the daily requests we receive for particular files or services, whether visitors access the site from paid advertisements, and from which countries those requests originate.

### Cookies

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer, which enables us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply to Toolkit.com. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Toolkit.com uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above) and third-party companies may use cookies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information (as described below).

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive a warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you may need cookies to participate actively in message boards, forums, polling and surveys.

### Use of Information

Toolkit.com uses information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the site or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

As described above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out our electronic newsletter and to enable users to participate in polls, surveys, message boards and forums. We send out newsletters to subscribers monthly, and may send out special editions when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing or that has happened.

As described above, we use tracking information to determine which areas of our site users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We track how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We do not track what individual users read. In addition, we track search terms entered in our search function as one of many measures of what interests our users, but this tracking is never associated with individual users and we don't track which search terms a particular user enters.

We create aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns. These aggregated statistics are used internally to better provide services to our users and may also be provided to advertisers, sponsors, and partners but again, they contain no individual personal or business information and cannot be used to gather such information. This allows our advertisers, partners, and sponsors to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs. Because we don't track the usage patterns of individual users, an advertiser, partner, or sponsor will never know that a specific user clicked their ad. We will not disclose any information about any individual user except to comply with applicable law, valid legal process, court order, government regulation, or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public or otherwise in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit this Website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

### Sharing of the Information

We use the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers, sponsors, and partners better understand our audience's demographics. This is essential to keeping certain services free to our users. Except as described above, we will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public or otherwise in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Consent

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of the information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post such changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

### California Privacy Rights

**YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS** \- California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits Members of Toolkit Media Group who are California residents to request certain information regarding the disclosure of any personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [customerservice@toolkit.com](mailto:customerservice@toolkit.com).

### Contact Us

Toolkit Members can access and correct their personal or business information online via [MyToolkit](http://www.toolkit.com/mytoolkit/index.aspx).

If you feel that this Website is not following its stated Privacy Policy, you may contact us via email at [customerservice@toolkit.com](mailto:customerservice@toolkit.com) Mon-Fri from 8:00 AM - 7:00 PM CT at 866-981-2677.
